VINAYAK KOLI

FRONTEND DEVELOPER vinayakkoli067@gmail.com +91-9590821007

Portfolio: "https://VinayakPortfolio.netlify.app/"

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Worked at Trivent soft services as a front-end developer since August 2021.

KEY SKILS

- React ,17,18
- React Routing
- Hooks
- Promises
- · Async and sync programming

TECHNICAL SKILLS

> Primary Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- React.js
- Redux

> Secondary Skills

- VS code
- Git Hub
- Windows Xp,7,8,10,11
- Linux

Projects

1.Vencer Paint

Name of the Project	VENCER PAINT		
Period	Aug 2021 to Oct 2021		
Description	This project is info site project. A major objective of this project is to manufacture and market a wide range of products for exterior and interior painting.		
Roles & Responsibilities	 To participate in requirement analysis. To write scalable, clean using React library. 		
UI Technology	HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, BOOSTRAP and REACT.JS		

2.SNIS

Name of the Project	SNIS		
Period	Nov 2021 to Jan 2022		
Description	This project is info site project. This project aims to connect Industrial Automation Solution providers with Electrical Switchgear Marketing Organizations in Karnataka.		
Roles & Responsibilities	 To participate in requirement analysis. To write scalable, clean using React library. To participate in requirement analysis. To write scalable, clean using React library. Revise, debug, update and refactor the code. Improve existing software. 		
UI Technology	HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, BOOSTRAP and REACT.JS		

3. Trivent soft services

Name of the Project	TRIVENT SOFT SERVICES	
Period	Feb 2022 to March 2022	
Description	It is a template-based project. This project aim is to inform Trivent clients to about their project they have completed till date.	
Roles & Responsibilities	 To participate in requirement analysis. To write scalable, clean using React library. 	
UI Technology	HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, BOOSTRAP	

4.Hebuni

Name of the Project	HEBUNI
Period	April 2022 to May 2022
Description	It is a template-based project. In addition, the project aims to provide information regarding their interior design work.
Roles & Responsibilities	 To participate in requirement analysis. To write scalable, clean using React library.
UI Technology	HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, BOOSTRAP

5. Varsha Road carriers

Name of the Project	Varsha road carriers		
Period	June 2022 to July 2022		
Description	It is a template-based project. In addition, the project aims to provide experience across the country with different kinds of transport.		
Roles & Responsibilities	 To participate in requirement analysis. To write scalable, clean using React library. Revise, debug, update and refactor the code. Improve existing software. 		
UI Technology	HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, BOOSTRAP and REACT.JS		

PROFILE LINK

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/vinayak-koli-6b1a54227/

• **GitHub**: https://github.com/vinayak677

WORK EXPERIENCE

- > Served as a front-end developer for Trivent Soft Services from August 2021 to August 2022.
- Worked as Mechanical design Engineer in Axis cades Pvt. Ltd. During the period of March 2019 to June 2021.
- Worked as Mechanical design Engineer in Neu-integrals Pvt. Ltd During the period of Jan 2018 to Feb-2019.

EDUCATION

Degree	Year of	Board/University	Specialization	Percentage	Class
	Passing				
Engineering	2016	VTU	Mechanical	61%	First class
P.U.C	2012	Pre-university	Science	60%	First class
		Education			
S.S.L.C	2010	Karnataka	-	88%	Distinction
		Secondary			
		Education Board			

ABOUT MYSELF

- Interest: Hobby like learning new skills.
- Known Languages: Communicate well in English, Hindi, Marathi and Kannada

WEBSITE LINKS & SOCIAL MEDIA:

Website https://vencerpaints.com/	Website https://snisindia.in/	Website https://sudarshanenterprises.in/
Website https://varsharoadcarriers.com/	Website http://hebuni.com/about/	

Portfolio and Practice Project:



